One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Beyond the hard rain, I saw a rainbow in the sky
hageshii ame no mukou kakaru niji o mita
We know the easy answers are all lies, yeah?
tayasui kotae wa uso da to shiru daro
Swear not to lose to the loudest voices
dekai koe nanka ni makenai to chikatte
Even if you face tomorrow alone, I hope you'll understand
anata hitori ni wakatte hoshii ashita
You, who gave me the time of my life
yume no you na jikan kureta anata
What am I to you,
watashi wa dou mieteru no
an angel or a devil?
sore ga tenshi ka akuma ka
Beyond the dawn, beyond the dawn
yoake no mukou yoake no mukou
I have so much I want to tell you
hanashitai koto takusan arun da
All my love, all my love,
ai kometa ai kometa
could never fit into the letters I wrote
tegami ni kakikirenai omoi da
Those tiny palms outstretched, searching for eternity
eien o sagashita chiisana te no hira
Luffy vs. Kizaru
Building A,
2nd Floor
Labophase
Marine HQ Vice Admiral
Pomsky
Bluegrass
Highest Authority of the World Government
Five Elders - Godhead of Science & Defense
St. Jaygarcia Saturn
DADDY
Conquering the world, believing in the future
sekai o seishite mirai o shinjite
What did you see, what did you learn?
nani o mite nani o shitte
Once again, I couldn't save a soul
mata daremo mamorenai no
My fault their voices're fading away
kiekakaru koe wa boku no sei
Don't even have time to hang my head
utsumuku hima mo nai no
Gravel marks on my palms
tenohira ni tsuku jari no ato
We're setting off again, my ship!
mata ugokidase boku no fune yo
Though I can't fly in the open skies
hiroi sora wa tobenai kedo
I can light up the deep sea
fukai umi wa teraseru kara
Which is why...
bokura wa
EVERYDAY owarenai
Everyday, we can't quit
EVERYDAY makerenai
Everyday, we can't lose
We've got something right here to defend
mamoru mono ga koko ni wa aru
Were my predictions all wrong?
yosou chigai kamo
But I can't stop anymore
tomarenai yo mou
We forge on, sharing the loneliness
kodoku o ima wakeai susumu
Don't chicken out now
ojikezukuna yo
I'm nothing like I used to be
ano hi no boku to chigau kara
No one can stand in my way
dare ni mo jama dekinai yo
So move!
saa doite
Conquering the world, believing in the future,
sekai o seishite mirai o shinjite
counting the endless nights
ikutsumo no yoru kazoete
What did you see, what did you learn,
nani o mite nani o shitte
taisetsu na koto ni kizuita no
to realize what's really important?